When I stood on the stage here and did a festival, or rather, a live show with various groups...
I'm a super dukumeki-sensei who will perform live here someday, go figure!
We made a vow here.
I had always wanted to do a solo live show someday,
I was really, really happy when it was announced,
The view I dreamed of?
I think an idol's dream equals the view of the arena,
When it's big, my dream expands and my heart fills with excitement,
I can't stop my heart from pounding.
I never thought that the day would come when I would be able to stand alone,
I didn't think so at the time of my debut,
But I really wanted to be on a big stage like my seniors one day,
Now it has come true? I am very happy to have reached the point where I can make it a reality.
What about your own production?
I have been active for about 8 years, and it has been slow,
I don't know if it's too late or too early,
I don't know if it is too late or too early, but it is really great to be here,
I think there are only a handful of people who are able to be here as a group,
I think it's very deep to be one of them,
I would like to do it someday.
I would like to do it someday, when I do my one-man show at Makuhari Messe,
About a month before the concert, the tickets for Makuhari were sold out,
I was really happy and my confidence grew,
I was so happy and confident, and I felt like I had done so much for the super-tokimeki publicity,
I was standing at Makuhari Messe with a big smug look on my face, as if to say, "I've made it all the way to the end.
The Yokohama Arena was also a venue that the staff prepared for us because they wanted to perform at Yokohama Arena,
I hope to be able to put on a confident face that says, "I've done it all again,
I felt gratitude for the expectations of the staff,
I felt it deeply in my heart.
When we performed at Makuhari Messe,
I hope we can become a group that can perform in such a large capacity again,
I hope we can grow even more and more,
I was hoping that we would continue to grow and develop even more and more,
I had a lot of opportunities to be on stage,
Of course, I had a wish to perform One More Love here someday,
But I never thought it would be a reality.
I wondered if we would really perform here,
We were wondering if we were really going to perform here, if people who love us would come here and support us,
I felt a little strange thinking that people who like us and want to support us would come here,
I felt a little strange.
It's done!
We got the gold medal!
You can see it in the picture, but if time presses on, it's going to be a big problem.
If I watch the wrong time, I'll give up...
Oh no!
I'm getting nervous.
I might cry.
I'm so nervous!
I'm so nervous about the first song
I don't think I'm going to cry.
I can't see your face for a second.
I cried yesterday.
Yesterday was 100 all.
I cried through the whole block.
Because you made me look good, you know.
I don't care anymore.
So now.
I'm the cutest girl ever because you dumped me.
I have the biggest crush on you in the history of my life.
It's the cutest thing I've ever seen.
I won't admit it, this is the damsel strikes back.
Okay, you're going to cover the story.
Be seated. You are seated.
Please.
I'm quite full of excitement and thrill. I am not so much nervous as I am thrilled and excited.
I was talking about the fact that it was already today with the members, and I was with them all yesterday, but they asked me in the car how I was feeling. I was in the car with the members yesterday, and they asked me, "How are you doing?
They asked me how I was doing in the car, and I told them that I would be back tomorrow. We kept talking about how unbelievable it was.
We had a rehearsal there,
We had rehearsals there, but we still couldn't imagine that there would be only fans who like us,
So I imagine that when we stand up, they will be really moved by our performance.
But I don't know if they will cry or be happy when they actually see the stage in front of them until I stand up,
That's what I'm most nervous about.
I'm nervous because they don't tell me.
The first song was really moving, even though it was me,
I'm sure I'm going to cry because I can sing the whole song.
I want to sing calmly and clearly.
This is the first time for me to perform, and I've been wanting to tell everyone about it for a long time,
I've been wanting to tell everyone about it for a long time, but I've been keeping it a secret,
It's called a moving stage,
I'm really looking forward to seeing how everyone will react to it,
Yesterday was the first time for me to see it at the rehearsal,
I saw it on our monitor on the moving stage.
I saw them on the monitors and they looked like big name artists,
I felt like it wasn't our show,
I'm sure the fans did, too,
I thought it would be a good way to make our fans feel that we had come this far in our crusade,
I would be happy if everyone could see it.
How do you feel now?
Wow!
I'm having so much fun!
It's just me, isn't it?
I'm sure you're wondering what it's all about.
But it's like an attraction.
I don't want to do anything.
But it just moves forward on its own.
It's really fun.
I'm looking at it from above, so I wonder if the millennial attempts will protect me more and more,
I can't see them.
I always see them, like the curry people,
I always look at them, I can't wait to see them.
I was making Base Mountain.
Base Mountain.
It's fun.
I'd like to say all of it, but,
It's so much fun.
Today is the first day of the Yokohama Arena love show,
We have been thinking, working, and working hard for the Yokohama Arena for the whole year 2023,
It's hard to believe that today, 41 hours from now, it will be over,
But I hope I can make everyone who comes to the show feel happy that I fell in love with them.
I will do my best to sing, express myself, and smile to the best of my ability.
I am very excited about how it will turn out,
I'm really excited about how it will turn out, but I'm more looking forward to it now that we've had a pretty good rehearsal.
But I am also looking forward to spending time with a record number of young dancers on the largest stage to date,
This will be my first live performance since I turned 20 years old, so I want to give my best performance so that I will have no regrets.
First of all, I will enjoy myself and do my best!
Happy Lovable!
Happy loveable!
No, it's vocalization.
It's also vocalization.
Happy loveable!
Happy loveable
I'm so excited... for you.
I'm so excited for you
I'm so excited, I'm so excited, I'm so excited. I'm excited. I'm excited.
But I don't know... I'm starting to feel it, but I can't really feel it.
We've been allowed to come to so many festivals, so I feel like it's really our show.
We'll be able to show you more and more love...
Thank you very much.
I feel like I'm going to be irresistible.
Oh no, what should I do?
Oh, I want to eat dinner!
I'm special... in this world.
Is that a problem? Is this a problem?
I'm so excited.
Why does it feel so good to me?
I'm just trying to understand.
It's fun.
I'm looking forward to it.
You call me when you're lonely.
I want to give you a big hug.
I don't know if I can do that.
You're so cute!
Wait, that's great.
I can't feel this.
I just did it.
Oh, no.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm teaching you.
No, no, no, no.
Oh no.
Oh, I can't do it anymore! I can't do it!
No, no, no!
Calm down!
I've endured it!
Tears!
It has to be this one.
Keyhole, keyhole, you can go.
Keyhole, keyhole.
Oh no.
You don't have to go through the keyhole.
Can you go to the keyhole?
But it's okay, there's always tomorrow.
There's always tomorrow.
Let's do it.
What, did you just yawn?
Did you just yawn?
Please help me.
Can you yawn?
I can yawn. I can.
You don't have to go through the keyhole.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll see you soon.
Thank you.
Oh, wow.
I guess I'm no good before the show.
Oh, is it this way?
Oh, this way, us.
Yes, we're fine.
Oh, I'm fine.
But Shu is probably not crying the most right now.
No, we're all the same.
No, he's not crying the most.
Julia's not leaning.
Julia is pretty hot.
A little.
She's really leaning.
Julia's not standing up.
You took a risk, but you did it, right?
We did it.
Let's go today! Chokietsu Dengenbu at Yokohama Arena
I know you'll be next to me.
Thank you very much for coming to Day 1 Love!
With Luton and Julianomi of Super Tokimeki Blue,
With Juliko and Anjulia of Super Tokimeki Purple,
I'm Hitoko Sakai, Hito-chan of Super Thrilling Red.
Are you ready to enjoy the first one-man live show of the year?
Yes!
Let's make time for TOKIMEKI together!
Everyone!
Will you fall in love with us by chance?
Nice meal.
Thank you.
Well, you'll just have to wait and see.
Okay, let's get to the act.
Go ahead.
Kanami jyunya!
Hitokun
Marukun
Akii
Hiyori
Super Tokimeki Advertising Department
Bakun
★Oh-kun, I'm here for a snack★
12, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
I can do it.
I can do it. Hang in there.
You're cute, cute
Don't cry, it's so cute
It's so hard to relax
Yeah, no problem.
Okay, okay, I'm coming in.
Come on, let's go.
Oh, I don't know if I can do it. I don't know if I can do it.
Who is that coming from?
Thank you for watching.
He's looking down a lot.
Oh, he's looking down a lot.
Oh-kun is looking down.
Ohkun is so cute.
Oh, he's just sitting there.
How is he? How is he? How's it going? How is it?
How's it going?
Eight.
Nine.
Cheers
Let's go for it!
You're going too fast!
Cheers
It's the Tokyo Olympic War we're going to live someday!
ED
I feel like it's going to come true
I'm chasing after it and can't reach it
But
I reached out my hand again
Every time you call my name
Every time we laugh together
I'm glad I didn't give up
I'm glad I didn't give up on you.
Will you always love me?
Will I always love you?
Even now.
A second into the future
Let's go!
It's going to be okay
I want to make it come true, I want to make it come true
Without a moment's pause
With our hearts
We'll keep on thrilling
Don't change, don't stop
How I wish again
To be pretentious
I believe in time
And that's why I've come to know
You and your youth
I'm alive with bangs
Thanks to your make-up artist.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
Help me.
Oh, no.
I made a mistake.
Yes. So, thank you all for taking time out of your precious time to come and see us today.
Yes. I am so happy that we were able to make it to this day without incident.
There have been many things that have happened in the process of coming this far, and there have been times when I felt like giving up,
There were times when I felt like giving up, times when things didn't go well, but I knew that I could do it.
I believe in myself, and I have continued to do so without giving up or running away,
I think that I was able to do it by seeing this view today.
Thank you for all your support and love.
I believe that the feeling of love is the strongest, most powerful power,
If you love something, you can do anything,
I believe that you can do anything if you have the feeling of liking something,
Everyone here today is connected by a single love,
So, I would like to continue to strengthen that bond together with you all,
I hope to make that bond stronger and stronger with you all.
I stood on this stage a few years ago,
When I stood on the stage here a few years ago and performed at the Fez, or rather, when various groups performed here,
We vowed that one day we would perform live here, and that we would be a super-documentary commercial! We vowed to do it here.
Today we were able to fulfill it. We made our promise come true!
We want to continue to prove to everyone that dreams can come true if you don't give up,
We want to continue to prove to everyone that dreams can come true if you don't give up.
We have welcomed many members of the publicity department at the venue like this,
We have come this far,
We are a team overflowing with love,
The staff cried and the members started crying,
The staff cried, and the members started to cry,
Even as I'm talking to you now,
I'm talking to you now, there are some members of the advertising department who are crying here and there,
I feel that we are a team overflowing with love,
I am very proud and grateful for that.
I never expected so many people to come to this event,
I never expected so many people to come,
I really didn't expect so many people to show up.
I started saying their names one by one when we were assembling the engine in the back of the room,
I wonder if everyone was listening.
I wonder if everyone heard it,
When I said "Kanami," they all shouted it out together,
When I was in the back, they kept calling me "Aki-chan",
I am always thankful for that at the live concerts,
I'm always thankful for that, but I'm really happy that so many people like me,
It was the moment when I felt how happy I was to have so many people like me and call me Aki-chan.
Our feelings of love for you all,
Our feeling of love for you all turned into like, like, like, like, like,
I love you all so much,
I think I was able to deliver to you all, this heart, this feeling, this feeling in my heart, this feeling in this tiny place, exploded,
I think we were able to deliver it to all of you.
I think that you all love us very, very much...
Thank you very much.
Thank you for all the love.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please.
Please, please, please.
I think I'll decide not to cry for 3 days, but I cried.
Not after the first day.
We made it through rehearsal.
No, we didn't.
I didn't practice 100% today.
It didn't work.
I knew it. It's a no-no.
It's no good if the staff cries.
The staff...
I want them to cry when they get on stage.
Because if they come to Corona, we won't know.
I can do the event tomorrow.
I cried.
Crying
I cried
How was it this time?
From Morimoto-san
I received a gift from Mr. Morimoto
Thank you, Morimoto san!
Every Tuesday at 23:30
Genesee
As a DJ
I work with Morimoto san
I'm doing a radio show with Morimoto san
Please listen to BFM if you like.
The surprise is over.
Are you waiting?
Yeah, I think so.
Let's go for it.
Mmm-hmm.
Food after a concert is the best.
Like at Makuhari, I get hungry during the show.
It's so good!
We couldn't eat enough of it. Everyone sent us photos.
I'll take care of it!
See you tomorrow! Bye bye!
Sorry I couldn't make it here today.
I'll see you on Friday.
DAY 1 love is over!
Thank you for your hard work!
Wow! The view is beautiful!
It was so beautiful that I wondered if I had really lost a thousand years of my life.
I'm so happy that we can now do this kind of karaoke.
But I don't really feel that we are all doing this together.
Yes, it is. It feels strange.
It's over, but still...? We're doing the side thing?
What's that? It's like, "Oh, tomorrow, DAY 1 is already over.
So it's already over.
He seems sad that tomorrow will be over too.
It's a little sad to see the end of something you've been looking forward to for more than a year.
It's sad.
Well, let's not be sad.
Let's do our best tomorrow!
I'll do my best!
I'll go to Vita Gohan afterwards.
I'll definitely go.
I've decided to go to sushi.
I'll be waiting for you.
I also want to eat yakiniku.
Then let's go to all of them.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best tomorrow too.
Then I will go and prepare for tomorrow.
Tomorrow is youth,
I wrote a lot of love-related one-liners today,
Tomorrow is youth.
I want to be young with you.
I'm saying.
Rocco, everyone.
What is it, Meegly, Meegly? And so on,
I was happy to see a kid with Hugh's autograph ball.
I really want to bring a lot of them because they are precious Rocco.
The unknown landscape is still in front of us.
Come on, let's go wherever you want.
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday, after the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my malignant heart, I paint shards of the future to guide me.
Subtitle: Kiyohiroiyo
I can still say it now
When you're lost, remember the reason for your tears
I'll try to smile even when it's raining
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye Good bye Yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a rainbow, rainbow pools, rainbow pours, rainbow pianos
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, Good bye, I was there yesterday
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a rainbow, crossing the clouds of tears
I'm wearing a rainbow dress
Please subscribe to our channel!